{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1800","name":"Wendy's","address":"6601 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207","owner":"Douglas Corp. of Michigan","licenseNumber":"221958","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365","coords":"-83.00613,42.34575","geojson":{"id":"1800","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.006129378,42.345752313]},"properties":{"name":"Wendy's","owner":"Douglas Corp. of Michigan","address":"6601 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"221958","establishmentid":"1800","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365","most_recent_license_date":"5/26/2020"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5317","name":"Comfort Cafe","address":"6533 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"51622615","name":"Le Petit Dejeuner","address":"6470 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1882","name":"City Pekin Chinese Food","address":"6905 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"1188","name":"Church's Fried Chicken #345","address":"6931 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"5161","name":"Southern Fire Bistro & Lounge","address":"575 Bellevue St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"3203","name":"Happy's Pizza #11","address":"6412 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"777","name":"Curis Big Boy Restaurant","address":"7033 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2764","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza #164","address":"500 Mt Elliott St","zipcode":"48207"},{"establishmentid":"2242","name":"Tim Hortons","address":"7201 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48214"},{"establishmentid":"5108","name":"Riverwalk Cafe Mt. Elliott","address":"120 Mt Elliott Rd","zipcode":"48207"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"52513","inspectionDate":"2020-08-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at restroom handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"No Soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-08-21T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Inside the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Missing Wall plugs","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"On top of the Table(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"Missing Hair Restraints/Covering","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."}]},{"inspectionid":"49232","inspectionDate":"2019-09-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Missing Wall plugs","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"BEVERAGE AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Cabinet(s) (lower)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"48512","inspectionDate":"2019-07-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"door(s)","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the bottom of Door","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Litter/debris","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Under the Hot holding unit","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"43390","inspectionDate":"2018-09-12T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"heated-air hand dryer","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (WOMEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Hand dryer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2018-09-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Light fixture","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"juncture","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"At customer seat booths Coved molding","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DINING AREA","subLocation":"Under the Beverage Dispenser","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2018-09-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39685","inspectionDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly date marked","subProblem":"Longer than 7 days stored at 41 degrees f","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"On the Shelf","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide proper date marks as stated above."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \r\n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Microwave oven door seals and cavities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Microwave Oven(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean as required above."}]},{"inspectionid":"36144","inspectionDate":"2016-08-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Fire suppression system","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Missing Light bulb(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-202.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise approved, light bulbs shall be shielded, coated, or otherwise shatter-resistant in areas where there is exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Light shielding","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"Missing Light Shield(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate light shields and end caps or shatter-proof bulbs."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1800"}}